<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flomb Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.flomb.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Flomb Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:44 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.flomb.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tekton Dashboard RCE and Kubernetes API Proxy</title>
      <link>https://blog.flomb.net/posts/tekton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:44 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.flomb.net/posts/tekton/</guid>
      <description>This is the story of how I found two vulnerabilities in the Tekton CI/CD Dashboard component that allow remote code execution and a potential node takeover if deployed in read/write mode as well as pre-authenticated access to the Kubernetes API server in all modes.&#xA;Both vulnerabilities were treated as intended and are thus still exploitable. The documentation was changed and the default mode is now read-only instead of read/write.&#xA;It started when I stumbled upon an unusual finding during an assessment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIL: SNI-Based Auto Certificate Generation Is a Thing</title>
      <link>https://blog.flomb.net/posts/autotls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 15:44:45 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.flomb.net/posts/autotls/</guid>
      <description>I recently stumbled upon a great writeup which explained how it is possible to get a SSRF from SNI to hit the Azure VM Instance Metadata Service(IMDS). Inspired, I started scanning for this behaviour within a bug bounty scope. Not finding a single target, I proceeded to scan for the more &amp;ldquo;generic&amp;rdquo; finding of SNI based SSRF which yielded some interesting results.&#xA;To be honest, I did not even know that SNI SSRF is a thing, so let&amp;rsquo;s start with that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://blog.flomb.net/posts/databricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 15:19:43 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.flomb.net/posts/databricks/</guid>
      <description>The following write-ups detail a privilege escalation vulnerability in Databricks that I discovered during my time at a previous employer. Due to contractual obligations, the post only contains links to external resources. For political reasons, there are three versions of the same write-up with varying degrees of detail.&#xA;Securing Databricks cluster init scripts Securing Databricks cluster init scripts SEC Consult mirror Bypassing cluster isolation in Databricks Platform </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://blog.flomb.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:51:52 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.flomb.net/about/</guid>
      <description>Simple, mostly security oriented, personal blog.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
